Without front end-developers, this is what the web will look like.
如果没有前端开发者 互联网就会变成这样
Pretty boring, right? No design.
很无聊 对吧？没有设计
No interaction. No good.
没有互动 什么酷炫的功能都没有
Without modern front-end development,
没有现代前端开发者的话
all of your favorite sites would be unrecognizable,
你喜欢的所有网站都变得毫无特色 认不出来
Google, Facebook, that cat blog you secretly like.
包括 Google Facebook 你偷偷关注的猫咪博客
With Udacity, you'll learn the foundational programming languages
在优达学城 你将学习基本的网络编程语言
of the web and build projects that will show off your new-found skills.
并通过构建项目来展示新学的技能
You'll start with HTML,
你将从所有网站的构建基石 HTML 开始
the building block of every website, text, links, images.
并学习文本 链接和图片
You'll then learn CSS so you can style your own website with layout, fonts and colors.
然后 你将学习 CSS 以便使用布局 字体和颜色为你的网站设定样式
Okay, too many colors.
好吧 颜色有点太多了
More and more of the web is being taken off the traditional computer screen and
越来越多的网络内容不再面向传统的计算机屏幕
adapted for any number of other screen shapes and sizes.
而是针对各种其他屏幕形状和尺寸调整设计模式
You'll build a portfolio site that functions well and looks good on a phone,
你将构建一个能正常运行并且在手机 电视和冰箱上显示效果良好的
a TV and a fridge?
作品集网站
Okay. Then we'll dive deep into the web's most popular programming language.
然后我们将深入了解最热门的网络编程语言
You'll learn what's needed to get started and use
你将学习以创新方式开始使用面向对象的
object-oriented JavaScript and the DOM in a creative way.
JavaScript 和 DOM 需要掌握的知识
With this understanding of JavaScript,
掌握这些 JavaScript 知识后
you'll have the ability to add amazing levels of interaction to,
你将能够添加精彩的互动功能
hold on, this does not look.
等等 这个看起来不太正常
This is embarrassing.
这有点尴尬
One second.
稍等
Throughout the process you'll learn how to troubleshoot and problem solve
在此过程中 你将学习如何像真正的程序员一样
like a real programmer. I should do this and that.
排查和解决问题 我应该这么修正
That should do it. And a little longer. There we go.
应该没问题了 再看看 没问题了
Finally, we'll get you comfortable with optimizing
最后 我们将帮助你完善你的网站
your websites and working with various APIs and different frameworks.
并使用各种 API 和不同的框架
The web is constantly changing and
网络瞬息万变
there are new and better tools popping up all the time.
更棒的新工具不断涌现
While we can't cover everything,
虽然我们不能介绍所有知识
by the end of the program you'd be prepared to
但是学完这门课程后
build off of the foundations you learned here,
你将能够运用所学的基础知识
and tackle all sorts of new technologies in the future.
掌握日后遇到的各种新技术
We're excited for you to start.
我们期待着马上开始学习了